Bryan Schneller

Full-Stack Web Developer

730 Branniff Dr. Cary, NC 27513 (484) 894-4578 bryan.schneller@gmail.com

OVERVIEW

After passionately building my web development skills for more than a year, I am excited and highly motivated to enter the web development field and bring my varied skills and interests to a dynamic team. Eight years of experience in the brain injury rehab field have honed my planning, organization and communication skills.

SKILLS

I have experience building full-stack web applications using HTML CSS and JS, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB and Mongoose, PostGreSQL and Sequelize, and using Git and Github in a team setting. I enjoy the challenge of learning new technologies to contribute to humankind's greatest invention.

EXPERIENCE

Wegmans, Cary, NC - Cashier (part-time)

AUG 2023 - PRESENT

- Provide a positive customer experience with thoughtful, individualized service
- Dynamically organize items for efficient and optimal bagging while handling cash transactions

Community Partnerships, Inc., Raleigh, NC - Rehabilitation Specialist

OCT 2022 - JUN 2023

- Administered formal and informal assessments to create a treatment plan in order to prepare individuals for employment and independence
- Implemented person-centered treatment plans and carried out therapy sessions to address needs relating to cognitive rehabilitation, therapy and counseling, case management, and occupational preparation
- Schedule sessions and create plans to track and report treatment outcomes

Success Rehabilitation, Inc., Quakertown, PA - Cognitive Rehabilitation Specialist

FEB 2017 - SEP 2022

- Administered standardized assessments and evaluations to determine individual strengths, weaknesses, and potential strategies
- Developed and implemented individualized treatment programs to address identified needs

 Functioned as on-call administrator to address staffing and maintenance issues and perform company-wide communications as needed

EDUCATION

University of Pittsburgh, PA - Bachelor's of Science, Psychology (Cum Laude) SEP 2009 - MAY 2013

Solid academic foundation in the study of psychology including research methods, and biological, cognitive, and neuroscience aspects

UNC Full-Stack Web Development Course, Chapel Hill, NC

NOV 2023 - PRESENT

Accelerated program focused on independent coding and team project-management skills in technologies including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express.js, Handlebars, React, Node.js, SQL and NoSQL databases, MERN stack, Git, Github, and the Agile development framework